<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chitreshblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on chitreshblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:02:50 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Her</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/remembering-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:02:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/remembering-her/</guid>
      
      <description>Remembering her
The song &amp;lsquo;remembering her&amp;rsquo; is just an instrumental of keys there is something really mysterious and dark about that song
Whenever I listen to it I find my self imagining me walking on a empty road in a forest full of Sakura blossom and later there is a crossroad
I pick one path and keep walking while still being in the forest of Sakura blossom there is a shop in the forest I find two people wearing masks as I am passing them , they look at me and keep staring at me and once I pass them I find myself at another crossroads</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A group of friends - 3rd September</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-of-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:02:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-of-friends/</guid>
      
      <description>Well now you might be wondering what&amp;rsquo;s this third September well
That&amp;rsquo;s the day I joined a place (let&amp;rsquo;s keep that a secret)
I met a bunch of new people there I met a guy we became friends and his friends became my friends
I had a lot of fun at that place they made me smile laugh enough though I was in a lot of pain
I went to eat out with them every Saturday and Sunday we discussed everything business, studies, cricket and what not</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feelings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/feeings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:02:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/feeings/</guid>
      
      <description>Well well where do i start umm
Lets start with feelings how do i feel at the moment ? I feel anxious about the future
There is so much happening in the world rightnow trying to keep up with all of that sometimes gets you demotivated
Also i am tired, i need to find a way through which I can distribute my energy wisely
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what i am talking right now i can&amp;rsquo;t express it i am not sad and i am not happy either</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:04:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      
      <description>About Me Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m chitresh, an aspiring software developer with a strong passion for technology,design and finance. Welcome to my personal blog where I document my journey of learning and building new stuff.
My Interests Programming Languages Quantitative finance Data Engineering/Science Ml Web Dev Graphic Design Learning Journey Currently, I am diving deep into the following areas:
HFT with C++ ML/DS/DSA/Dev Design Contact Me Feel free to connect with me via chitreshpoojary990@gmail.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:02:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello World! Welcome to my first blog post on chitreshblog.
Why did I start this ? To share what i am doing , basically i am doing new stuff like everyday so sharing on instagram everyday is such a drag plus a lot of people asked me why did I stop my last blog after my first post because It was too much of writing code but eh I found a simpler way,so expect new blogs</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/firstdesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:02:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/firstdesign/</guid>
      
      <description>Coming soon </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
